{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"14/2",
			"answer":"14/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"45/0.09",
			"answer":"45/0.09",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"16/2",
			"answer":"16/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"37/0.009",
			"answer":"37/0.009",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.43/0.07",
			"answer":"0.43/0.07",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"64/8",
			"answer":"64/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"24/4",
			"answer":"24/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.8/0.09",
			"answer":"7.8/0.09",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"30/3",
			"answer":"30/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.61/0.2",
			"answer":"0.61/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"388/7",
			"answer":"388/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"858/8",
			"answer":"858/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"260/9",
			"answer":"260/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"192/6",
			"answer":"192/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"630/3",
			"answer":"630/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"352/32",
			"answer":"352/32",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"360/15",
			"answer":"360/15",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"420/60",
			"answer":"420/60",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"136/68",
			"answer":"136/68",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"459/27",
			"answer":"459/27",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2160/50",
			"answer":"2160/50",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4510/33",
			"answer":"4510/33",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2521/63",
			"answer":"2521/63",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8381/96",
			"answer":"8381/96",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3335/22",
			"answer":"3335/22",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}